# Vera Liu

## Front-end engineer



### **About Me**

I have been working in CommonWealth Magazine Group as a front-end engineer for five years.

I am a person who is positive, optimistic, outgoing and who has the courage to take any challenges.

Currently, I am learning web3-related knowledge and hope to apply it in conjunction with my existing knowledge in the future.

## Education

(2011-2015)

**FU JEN UNIVERSITY** 

**Bachelor of Chemistry** 

## (2017-2018)

INSTITUTE FOR INFORMATION INDUSTRY. III

Training class for Web/APP frontend engineers

## Contact

- veraaaaaliuuuuu@gmail.com
- <a href="https://github.com/veraaaaaLiu">https://github.com/veraaaaaLiu</a>
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/yiling-liu-vera/

#### Skills

- vue (vue2/vue3/nuxt2/nuxt3)
- svelte (svelteKit)
- firebase
- qit
- figma

## **Experiences**

(2018 - present)

CommonWealth Magazine Group

#### FRONT-END ENGINEER 4Y+

- Develop and Maintain company website
  - o <u>smiletaiwan-lesson-plan</u>
  - o TRIPs
- Landing page
  - sdgs / sdgs-podcast
  - o <u>futureMindset</u>
  - taipower
  - smiletaiwan-sustainability
  - o <u>smiletaiwan-20anniversary</u>
- Develop tools to Increase work efficiency.
- Design-system

## (2020 - present)

#### FREELANCE DEVELOPER 2Y+

- Hospital dashboard
- · School official website
- Reservation system + Line liff
- Accounting system
- Landing page

